坚持住 我知道
JOHN: Hang on. I know.
嗯
KATE: Mm.
你做得很好
You're doing so good.
你做得很好 没事儿吧?
JOHN: You're doing so good. You all right?
没事 好的
Yeah. Okay.
马修斯医生请到护士站
WOMAN [O VER PA]: Dr. Matthews to the nurses' station.
请问
JOHN: Excuse me.
我太太快生了 我们预约了惠勒医生
My wife's in Iabor. We called ahead for Dr. WheeIer.
请把表填下
MAN: I just need you to fiII this out, pIease.
谢谢 宝贝 坐下吧
Thank you. Have a seat, hon.
我马上过来 好
I'II be right up. KATE: Yeah.
没事吧? 没事
Okay? Okay.
第一胎? 不 不 第三胎了
Is this your first? No, no, it's our third.
先生 请在这儿签名
MAN: Sir, can you sign here?
我们准备叫她杰西卡
We're gonna name her Jessica.
生命体征正常
WOMAN: VitaIs Iook good.
约翰在哪儿?
KATE: Where's John?
我老公呢? 放松
Where's my husband? MAN: Just reIax now.
会很顺利的
Everything's gonna be okay.
怎么了? 你们在干什么?
What's happening? What are you doing?
很遗憾没保住
I'm so sorry for your Ioss.
什么? 胎儿死了
What? Your baby's dead.
不 没死呀 活着的
No, it's not dead. It's aIive.
你在说什么呀?还在动呢
What are you taIking about? It's moving.
非常遗憾 我们很抱歉
It's a terribIe Ioss. We're so sorry.
放松吧 不!
Just reIax. No!
什么?不 不 不 给我打麻药 让我麻醉
What? No, no, no. Put me to sIeep. I wanna be asIeep.
来不及了 不!
MAN: It's too Iate for that. No!
没事的 宝贝 你做得很好
It's okay, you're doing great.
你在干嘛? 你在干嘛?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
你可能会因拉扯而有点痛
MAN: You might feeI some tugging.
上帝呀 这不是真的
Oh, my God. This isn't happening.
恭喜你 科尔曼太太 是女孩
CongratuIations, Mrs. CoIeman. It's a girI.
是的 凯特 日有所思夜有所梦
WOMAN: Yes, Kate, your dreams can be a manifestation of your emotions.
这是你的身心面对压力
It's your body and mind's way of deaIing...
和曾经的痛苦的方式
...with the stress and grief of what happened.
如果是与死产无关呢?
What if this has nothing to do with the stiIIbirth?
你觉得会是什么原因?
What do you think it's about?
这个周末我们将首次去见孩子们
We're seeing kids for the first time this weekend.
也许这噩梦...
And maybe the nightmares....
也许我还没准备好领养
Maybe I'm just not ready to adopt yet.
前两天晚上我开车回家 路过酒铺
I drove by the wine shop on the way home the other night.
你停车了吗?
Did you stop?
没 想停 有这个冲动
No. Wanted to. The thought went through my brain, you know?
不是买给自己 不是...
It wasn't for myseIf. It wasn't....
我只是觉得万一有客人来 能以美酒款待 多好啊
I just thought it wouId be nice to have a bottIe handy, in case we had guests.
但你没有进去
But you didn't go in.
嗯嗯
Mm mm.
我的解释是...
The key, to me...
...不是你不想
...is not that you had the urge...
...但是你抵抗住了
...but that you resisted it.
如果你没有做好准备 你可是无法完成家庭作业的
You wouIdn't have made it through the home study if you weren't ready.
但 最终...
But, uItimateIy...
...你得做出决定
...you have to decide.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 宝贝
Honey, heIIo.
我看看 是你画的吗?
Let me see. Ooh. Did you paint this?
老师辅导的
[SIGNING]
真是漂亮的蝴蝶 太棒了
It's a beautifuI butterfIy. It's fantastic.
真是棒极了 真棒
Really wonderfuI. Good.
走吧 好冷呀
Let's go. I'm coId.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
啊!
Ah!
麦克斯!
Max!
别扔球了!
Stop throwing!
我在工作呢
I'm working.
抱歉
不 宝贝 对不起
KATE: No, honey, I'm sorry.
稍微歇一会儿 好吗?
Just take a break for a IittIe whiIe, okay?
因为妈妈在弹琴 好吗?
Because Mommy's trying to pIay. Okay?
爸爸来了
Daddy's here.
我的 嘿
Mine. Hey.
嗨 抱歉 训练晚了点
Hi. JOHN: Sorry, practice went a IittIe Iate.
没事
KATE: It's all right. DANIEL: Whoa.
好了 硬汉 给我 耍赖
JOHN: Okay, tough guy. Give me that. DANIEL: Wicked.
不 不
No, no.
投篮 投篮 投 投 投
JOHN: Shoot it, shoot it. Go, go, go, go.
不 耶!击掌
DANIEL: No. JOHN: Yes! Give me five.
嘿 怎么样? 丹尼尔
Hey, how did it go? DanieI.
挺好的
Fine.
嘿
JOHN: Hey.
好了
Okay.
就玩5分钟 打到最后一关了
DANIEL: Five minutes. I'm at the Iast IeveI.
别玩电玩了 去刷牙
JOHN: No more video games. Brush your teeth.
太不公平了 没存档呢 老爸行行好 好吗?
DANIEL: That's no fair. It won't save. Come on, Dad, pIease?
今晚我们读点别的吧
好吧
我等了整整一夜...
为了见我新生的小妹妹
不过...
当妈妈和爸爸回到家时
妈妈告诉我说
我的小妹妹去了天堂
我为妹妹去了天堂而感到高兴
但我真希望在此之前能先见她一面
小杰西卡是天使么?
[SIGNING]
是的 是只漂亮的小天使
我会拥有一个新姐妹么?
我不知道
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉 抱歉 抱歉
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
上帝呀
God.
你闻起来真香
You smeII good.
好吧
Okay.
AII right.
我不能再像这样了
I have to stop being Iike this.
我知道
JOHN: I get it.
我很激动 很高兴
I'm very excited, I'm happy.
还有些紧张
I get nervous.
真得很害怕
I'm really scared.
上次我失去孩子 也是这种感觉
Last time I feIt all of this was right before I Iost the baby.
我不想让你觉得 是为了我 才必须经历这些的
I don't want you to feeI Iike we have to go through with this for my sake.
不只是...不是为了你
It's not just It's not for you.
我想弥补对杰西卡的爱
I wanna take the Iove we feIt for Jessica...
我想把这份爱给真正需要的人
...and I wanna give it to somebody who really needs it.
你准备好了吗? 宝贝
Are you sure, hon?
是的
Yes.
想堆雪人吗? 好啊
GIRL 1: Wanna make a snowman? GIRL 2: Sure.
外面好冷呀
GIRL 3: It's really coId out here.
嘿 别这样
GIRL 4: Hey, stop it.
嗨 嗨
WOMAN: Hi. KATE: Hi.
很高兴你们来了
So gIad you couId make it.
我们也很高兴 是呀 终于来了 对吧?
So are we. Yeah, finally, right?
很高兴见到你 感谢你们的到来
So good to see you. ABIGAIL: Thank you for coming.
真不错 随便逛下吧
This is really something. ABIGAIL: So go take a Iook around.
别惹麻烦哟 好 好
Stay out of troubIe. JOHN: Yeah, yeah.
看 孤儿雪人
Look at the snow orphan.
孤儿雪人?
KATE: Snow orphan?
孤雪人?
Uh, snorphan?
嘿 不 给玛丽修女看看
GIRL: Hey. WOMAN: No, show it to Sister Mary.
慢点 慢点 你抓不到我
WOMAN: SIow down, sIow down. GIRL 1: You can't catch me.
谁说的
GIRL 2: Yes, I can.
你好?
ESTHER: HeIIo?
嗨
Hi.
这些都是你画的?
Are all these paintings yours?
是的 喜欢吗? 很棒
Yes. Do you Iike them? They're remarkabIe.
谢谢
Thank you.
我叫艾斯特 你呢?
My name is Esther. What's yours?
约翰 很高兴认识你
John. Nice to meet you.
我能坐下来吗? 当然
Can I take a seat? Of course.
看孩子们欢聚一堂 永不会感到厌烦
I never get tired of watching these kids enjoy the party.
的确 真后悔之前我们还犹豫不决
It really is. I'm so sorry we didn't do this sooner.
怎么会 这可是重大决定
Don't be. It's a big Ieap.
决定领养一个孩子 可不是件容易的事
Adopting an oIder chiId is not an easy decision to make.
约翰去卫生间了
KATE: John's in the bathroom.
他会找到我们吗? 想去找找他吗?
ABIGAIL: Think he'II find us? Do you wanna go Iook for him?
这个灵感是从哪儿来的? 我的画都是有故事的
Where did you get the idea for this one? My paintings aIways teII stories.
这幅讲的是找不到幼狮的悲伤母狮
This one's about a sad mother Iion who can't find her cubs.
她在笑 她梦见了她的孩子
She's smiIing. She's dreaming about her babies.
这是唯一能让她高兴的事
It's the onIy thing that makes her happy.
真希望她能找到孩子们 她会的 看
I hope she finds them. She wiII. Look.
他们在森林里迷路了 他们很害怕...
They were Iost in the jungIe, and they were so scared...
...因为妈妈不在身边
...because they didn't have a mother.
就在他们以为将孤独一辈子时...
Just when they thought they'd be aIone forever...
...他们发现妈妈就在树下睡觉
...they found their mother asIeep under this tree.
她醒来的时候 梦想就成真了
Now when she wakes up, her dream wiII have come true.
母子团聚 真让人吃惊 你想出来的?
She'II have her famiIy again. Amazing. You came up with that story?
我好像听到他的声音了 对
KATE: I think I hear his voice down here. Yes.
嘿 我来介绍 这是我妻子 凯特
Hey. I want to introduce you. This is my wife, Kate.
凯特 这是艾斯特
Kate, this is Esther.
你好
HeIIo.
你好吗? 很高兴认识你
How are you? Nice to meet you.
这些都是她画得
She painted all these.
真的? 是的
Really? Yeah.
了不起呀 真是太棒了
These are fantastic. These are really wonderfuI.
谢谢 你在哪儿学的?
Thank you. Where did you Iearn how to do this?
大概是因为我有大量的练习时间吧
I've just had Iots of time to practice, I guess.
这里真的有些无聊了
It's really boring here.
这里无聊?
It's boring here?
如果你觉得无聊 为什么不参加派对呢?
If you're so bored, why aren't you down at the party?
毫无意义 以前都没人搭理我
I've never really seen the point of it. Nobody's ever taIked to me before.
可能我有些与众不同吧
I guess I'm different.
与众不同也没什么不好
There's nothing wrong with being different.
你俩倒是有很多共同点
JOHN: WeII, you two have a Iot in common.
我想人们会常说
ESTHER: I think peopIe shouId aIways...
过去的就让它过去...
...try to take the bad things that happen to them...
努力创造美好的未来
...and turn them into something good.
不是吗? 是的
Don't you? Yeah.
当然了
AbsoIuteIy.
她原籍是俄罗斯 但她英语出奇的好
ABIGAIL: She's originally from Russia, but it's amazing how strong her EngIish is.
她来美国才几年时间
She's onIy been in the country a few years.
你们收留其他国家的孩子?
You get chiIdren from other countries?
很少 一旦收留了 安置工作会比较麻烦
It's rare. But when we do, it's sometimes difficuIt to pIace them.
和她一起来美国的家人死于火灾
The famiIy that brought her to America died in a house fire.
火灾?
In a fire?
上帝呀
My God.
艾斯特刚好外出了
Esther bareIy got out.
她经历了很多事 但她是个特别的小女孩
She's been through a Iot, but this is an extraordinary IittIe girI.
她聪明伶俐 有着超出年龄的成熟
She's very bright. She's very mature for her age.
彬彬有礼 倒有点像个公主
And she's very weII mannered. She's a bit of a princess, actually.
在手腕和脖子上 总是戴着那些丝带
She wears those ribbons on her wrists and her neck all the time.
我也是
Mine too.
我们想给她取下来 但她不干
We had troubIe with her when we tried to take them off.
她和其他孩子相处的如何?
How does she get aIong with other kids?
需要和其他孩子互动时 她也做得很好
Oh, when she has to interact, she's great.
亲爱的?
Babe?
她似乎对我们很放得开 对
She really did seem to open up with us. Yeah.
我看她对你更放得开些
ABIGAIL: I thought she more than opened up with you.
你们似乎沟通得很好
You seem to have made quite a connection.
我可以把文件准备好 三周后你们再来吧
I couId get the paperwork together and see you back here in three weeks.
好的
AII right.
好耶!
Okey dokey.
有什么需要就给我电话吧
ABIGAIL: Call me if you need anything.
再见 好的 谢谢你
Bye. Okay, thank you.
那是T H
Oh, that's T H.
T H 对
T H. Yeah.
"麦克斯"是像这样吗?
And ''Max'' is Iike this?
对
KATE: Yeah.
很好
Good.
那是你们的房子吗? 现在也是你的了
Is this your house? JOHN: Now it's your house too.
嗨 甜心 嗨 看谁来了
KATE: Hi, sweetie. Hi. Look who's here.
你好麦克斯 我的名字是艾斯特
HeIIo, Max. My name is Esther.
她路上一直在练习
She's been practicing the whoIe way.
她能听见吗? 一点点
Can she hear? KATE: A IittIe.
她先天性失聪
She was born aImost compIeteIy deaf.
那个只是辅助她读唇语的
That just allows her to hear enough to read Iips.
没事的 我都拿上了
JOHN: That's all right, I got it.
这位是芭芭拉奶奶
JOHN: I'd Iike to introduce you to Grandma Barbara.
很高兴见到你
It's a pIeasure to meet you.
真可爱 我也很高兴见到你
That's precious. It's a pIeasure to meet you too.
丹尼
Danny.
这是艾斯特
This is Esther.
你好 丹尼尔
HeIIo, DanieI.
嘿
Hey.
为什么她穿成那样?
[WHISPERS] Why does she dress Iike that?
行了 别那样 问问而已
Come on. Stop it. I'm just asking a question.
啊!
Oh!
你们有钢琴? 对
You have a piano? Yeah.
想学弹琴吗? 很想学
WouId you Iike to Iearn how to pIay? I wouId Iove to.
喜欢吗?
Do you Iike it?
太完美了 那就好
It's perfect. KATE: Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
"谢谢"的手势怎么做?
How do you say ''thank you''?
谢谢 不客气
Thank you.
不客气
哇 看啊
JOHN: Wow, Iook at that.
怎么了? 怎么了? 怎么了?
What? What? What?
爸 看
DANIEL: Dad, Iook.
爸 你在哪儿找到的?
Dad. JOHN: Where did you get that?
爸 看 我正要击败特雷弗 真棒
DANIEL: Dad, Iook, I'm kiIIing Trevor. JOHN: Great.
爽
Yes.
谢谢
ESTHER: Thank you.
快 爸 我的独奏快结束了 快看呀
Come on, Dad. My soIo's gonna end. Hurry, Iook.
哇 真酷
Wow, cooI.
特雷弗 你真逊 闭嘴
DANIEL: Trevor, you suck. TREVOR: Shut up.
真是太棒了
KATE: That's fabuIous.
走吧 伙计们 太无趣了
Come on, guys. This is Iame.
我正要痛扁你
I was just about to beat you.
你喜欢 我就高兴了 宝贝
I'm gIad you Iike it, honey.
快来 伙计们
Come on, guys.
快 冻死我了
TREVOR: Hurry up, I'm freezing my ass off.
兄弟 都在这里了 上帝呀 手冻僵了
DANIEL: Dude, it's all in here. BO Y: Oh, God. My hands are freezing.
呀 真性感呀
DANIEL: Oh, man, she's hot.
让开 伙计 34页会爽翻你
Move over, man. Page 34 wiII change your Iife.
哇啊
Whoa.
看起来像你老母
This Iooks Iike your mom.
不
No.
艾斯特和玛克辛 看来相处得不错
Esther and Maxine seem to be getting aIong weII.
是呀
Yeah.
她怎么样了? 凯特
BARBARA: How's she doing, Kate?
艾斯特正在融入进来
Esther's fitting right in.
我是说玛克辛
I meant Maxine.
她在池塘边玩耍 就像什么也没发生过一样
She's pIaying by the pond Iike nothing ever happened.
她记不得了 对吧?
She doesn't remember, does she?
嗯 她没事
No. She's fine.
那你有什么打算?
So, what are your pIans?
让艾斯特先安顿好...
KATE: You know, probabIy get Esther settIed...
然后回去教书
...then go back to teaching.
他们好像不打算让你回去了
Thought they weren't gonna take you back.
不 我不是说耶鲁
No, I'm not taIking about YaIe.
我是说 我可能在家里授课
I'II just I'II probabIy give Iessons from home.
那可太糟了 多好的工作啊
That's too bad. That was a very good job.
又不是我想辞职的
WeII, I didn't quit because I wanted to.
我知道 你当时需要戒除酒瘾
I know. You had to have your moment of cIarity.
又要提戒酒互助课程
That is an A.A. term.
而我没去参加戒酒互助会 一样停止了酗酒
And I didn't go to A.A. I just stopped drinking.
大同小异 有时候我们都需要个醒钟
Same difference. We all need a wake up call sometimes.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 过来
KATE: Hi. Come here.
怎么了?
KATE: Yeah?
哦 嘿 我们被闪电吓到了
Oh, hey. We're scared of the Iightning.
快进来
Oh, come in.
我想睡爸爸旁边 等一下
I wanna sIeep next to Daddy. Hang on.
好的
Okay.
我待会儿打电话 看看是否一切都好
JOHN: I'm gonna call Iater, make sure everything's okay.
好 他们会喜欢你的设计的
Okay. They're gonna Iove your design.
记得接我电话哦 嗯
You gonna pick up the phone? Yeah.
好的
AII right.
艾斯特?
KATE: Esther?
Esther?
快点
Come on.
艾斯特 快点 要走啦!
Esther, come on, we gotta go!
我没看错吧
You gotta be kidding me.
哇噢...
KATE: Wow. Uh....
你们先上车好吗? 走吧
WiII you pIease go wait in the car? Come on.
亲爱的 这可不是学生装
Sweetheart, this isn't really a schooI dress.
但我喜欢啊 难道不漂亮吗?
But I Iike it. Don't you think it's pretty?
不错 确实很漂亮...
Yes, it's so beautifuI...
但穿起来也许不够舒适
...but I just don't think you're gonna be comfortabIe in it.
你的牛仔裤呢?
What about those jeans?
你是担心其他孩子会笑话我吧?
You're afraid the other chiIdren wiII Iaugh at me.
我记得你说过与众不同不是错
I thought you said there wasn't anything wrong with being different.
是的 说过 我是说过
Yes, you're right. You're absoIuteIy right.
好吧 开心点
Okay. Have fun.
请坐下 坐下
Take a seat, pIease. Take a seat.
别让我说第二遍
Don't make me ask again, pIease.
我们来了位新同学 名字叫艾斯特 科尔曼
Okay, this is our new student. Her name's Esther CoIeman.
希望大家能热情的欢迎她
And I'd Iike you all to make her feeI very weIcome today.
噢 看啊 小牧羊女来短信了 她想要回她的衣服
Oh, Iook. LittIe Bo Peep texted me. She wants her outfit back.
好吧 去找个位子
TEACHER: Okay, go take a seat.
好吧 大家把书翻到27页...
Okay, if everybody couId turn to Page 27....
不!
KATE: No!
不! 艾斯特 你在干嘛?
No! Esther, what are you doing?
快出来! 出来!
Get away from there! No!
不准在冰上玩! 告诉过你的!
You don't pIay near the water! You know that!
快点 出来!
Come on, get out!
麦克斯
ESTHER: Max.
真棒 真准
Sweet. BuII's eye.
太准了
Got you.
你开的枪? 我没想到威力会这么大
ESTHER: Did you kiII it? I didn't think it wouId hurt him.
帮它解脱了
Put it out of its misery.
它的痛苦 是你带来的 这是个意外
It's in pain, and it's your responsibiIity. It was just an accident.
你现在走掉 它也会活活饿死
If you waIk away now, it'II starve to death.
难道你想这样?
Is that what you want?
我做不来
I'm not doing it.
结束了
It's all right.
它现在去天堂了 你有病吗?
It's in heaven now. What's wrong with you?
水够热吗? 是的 谢谢
KATE: Is the water warm enough? ESTHER: Yes, thank you.
那洗吧 有事就叫我
KATE: Okay. Call me if you need anything.
艾斯特?
Esther?
艾斯特
Esther.
这门得开着
Open this door.
你在干嘛? 我向来都锁门的
What are you doing? I aIways Iock the door.
但我们家都不会锁
No, we don't Iock doors in this house.
那有人进来看见我怎么办?
But what if someone comes in and sees me?
没人会进来
Nobody's gonna come in.
有必要的话 我就站在这等你
Look, I'm gonna stand right here, if that's what you want.
那我唱歌给你听
ESTHER: I couId sing for you.
我以前常唱给修女听 好让她们知道我没事
I used to sing for the sisters so they wouId know I was all right.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 但是下不为例
AII right. But you know what? This is just for tonight.
你父母肯定费尽千辛万苦 才挑出了她
Your parents must have gone to a Iot of retard camps to find her.
看着路
Watch it.
你没事吧?
GIRL: Are you okay?
这是《圣经》吗?
Is this a BibIe?
怪物今天带了本《圣经》来学校
Jesus Freak brought a BibIe to schooI today.
嘿 要一起来吗?
GIRL 1: Hey, wanna come over?
很不错 你姐姐确实是个怪物
GIRL 2: Good one. Your sister's a totaI spaz.
她不是我姐姐
She's not my sister.
你居然真的这样做了
GIRL 2: I can't beIieve you did that.
噢 狗狗 你戴的是项圈吗 小狗狗?
Oh, IittIe doggy. Is this your coIIar, IittIe doggy?
不是 A 是A B
Not A. A, B.
弹得非常好
You did really good.
没有 不算好 弹错了11处
No, I didn't. I made Iike 1 1 mistakes.
但下次我会更努力
I'II do better next time.
老师把今天的事跟我说了
Your teacher toId me what happened today.
不想谈谈吗?
Don't you want to taIk about it?
没什么好谈的
There's nothing to taIk about.
我会一直守护你的 你知道的吧?
You know I'm here for you, right? You know that, right?
有个东西要给你看看
I got something I wanna show you.
我有个同样的小本用来写日记
I have one just Iike this that I use as a diary.
而你呢 可以用这个...
And I thought that maybe you and I couId use this one...
...做个剪贴薄
...for a scrapbook.
这是爸妈在结婚那天照的
That's Mommy and Daddy on their wedding day.
丹尼尔 摄于圣诞节早晨
That's DanieI, Christmas morning.
小家伙 麦克斯
Here's Max.
接着就是你
And there's you.
杰西卡是谁?
Who's Jessica?
麦克斯提起过她
Max taIks about her.
我虽未曾拥有 但我早已感受
KATE: ''I never heId you, but I feeI you.
你还未曾笑语 而我却已聆取
You never spoke, but I hear you.
即使命运让我们别离 但...爱你如一
I never knew you, but I Iove you.''
她怎么了?
What happened to her?
她在我肚子里夭折了
She died whiIe she was stiII in my tummy.
我们把她的骨灰撒在这儿
But we scattered her ashes here.
当这些花朵盛开的时候...
And as Iong as this pIant grows...
她就会与她们一同欢笑
...then part of her wiII be aIive inside it.
她本来会很幸福
She wouId have been Iucky.
因为你是最好的妈妈
You're a great mommy.
谢谢你 宝贝
Thank you, sweetheart.
谢谢你 我很欣慰
Thank you. It means a Iot.
你还好吗? 不错啊
JOHN: How are you? KATE: I'm good.
很有趣 艾斯特今天敞开心扉了
It's very interesting. Esther started to open up today.
是很有趣
JOHN: That's very interesting.
我有点感觉她像是我亲生的了
KATE: I'm starting to feeI Iike there's a reaI connection.
我也是
Me too.
别 亲爱的 别在这嘛 嘘
KATE: No, honey, not here. Shh.
他们睡着了
They're sIeeping.
宝贝 来吧 你会喜欢的
Baby, come here, you'II Iike it, beIieve me.
好吧 切入正题 不 不 不
Okay, Iet's get down to business. No, no, no.
那就 再多加点前戏
Okay, just for a second, then.
哈哈
Yeah.
不 不行 来嘛
No, no, no. Come on.
我必须去... 等下 等等嘛
I have to. Wait, wait, wait.
耶
Yeah.
喔! 噢 对不起
Ow! Oh, sorry.
噢 天啊
Oh, Jesus.
天啊 亲爱的 妈的!
Jesus, honey. Damn it.
艾斯特?
Esther?
我们得谈谈昨晚的事
We have to taIk about Iast night.
有必要吗? 有的
Do we? Yes, we do.
本来有些大人的事...
See, there are certain things that grown ups do...
是不该让小孩子看见的
...that chiIdren aren't supposed to see.
比如...昨晚的事
And that was one of them.
艾斯特 听我说
Esther, Iisten to me.
当大人们非常非常爱恋对方时...
When grown ups Iove each other very, very much...
他们希望能让对方感受到爱意
...they wanna show each other that Iove. Express it.
我懂 叫"操"
I know. They fuck.
这词哪都会出现 比如学校里
She couId've picked it up anywhere. ProbabIy at schooI.
她可不是骂脏话 她就指的那事
This wasn't something she overheard. I mean, she knew what it meant.
呵
Huh.
而且 她当时说话的样子...
And, babe, the way she said it is
完全不当回事
I don't even think she expected to get in troubIe over it.
好吧 晚上我们一起谈谈
WeII, we'II taIk to her about it tonight.
好吧
Fine.
那你有什么打算?
WeII, what did you have in mind?
呃 带她去见见布朗宁医生
No, I thought we couId take her to Dr. Browning.
她还不至于看心理医生吧
I don't think we need to take her to the shrink quite yet.
要知道 我们并不是很了解她
WeII, you know, we just don't know that much about her.
她以前的家人有可能是那种
The famiIy she stayed with couId've been Iike:
张嘴闭嘴就"操你妈的" 对不对?
''Pass the fucking potatoes'' at dinnertime, you know?
她当着我的面都敢说 那背着我们的时候呢?
If she's saying it to my face, what is she saying when we're not there?
我可不想她把麦克斯给带坏了
I don't want her exerting that kind of infIuence over Max.
我只是不想为句脏话而兴师动众
Anyway, I just don't want to make a big deaI out of one IittIe dirty word.
好吧 那他妈的多陪陪她
Fine. Fucking spend some time with her, then.
好的 臭婆娘
AII right, bitch.
来打雪仗吧!
GIRL: Let's have a snow fight!
好了 不准扔雪球
WOMAN 1: Come on, no throwing snowballs.
你好啊 邻居
WOMAN 2: Hey, neighbor.
好啊 最近都见不到你
Hey. Haven't seen you around IateIy.
这几天太忙了
JOHN: I've been pretty busy.
我不在的时候其他户主还是常聚会吗?
Has the homeowners' association been soIdiering on without me?
但有你会不一样
It's not the same.
呃 实际上 我想请你帮个忙
Um, actually, I had a favor to ask.
我有张大椅子要搬到楼上去...
I have a chair that I need moved upstairs...
...不知你能否抽空过来帮下我
...and I was hoping you couId come by and heIp me with that sometime.
行
Yeah.
行 没问题 谢谢
Yeah, sure. Good.
凯特和我说不定能帮上忙 告诉我们一声就行
Maybe Kate and I couId heIp you out. Just Iet us know.
那到时候叫你
I'II call you.
走吧 宝贝
Let's go, honey.
好的 我来看着你
MAN: Okay, I'm watching you.
布伦达爸爸说是你推的她
Brenda's father says that you pushed her.
不是的
That's not true.
我们只是在玩
We were just pIaying.
我发誓
I swear.
好吧 你知道怎么回事吗?
Okay. And did you see what happened?
她滑倒了
[SIGNING]
什么? 妈妈 她说的什么?
What? Mom, what's she saying?
她要你把面包和黄油递给她
She wants you to pass the bread and butter.
又没问你 嘿 别吵架哈
Wasn't asking you. JOHN: Hey, now.
你就不能正常的吃饭吗?
Can you eat normaI?
正常人就像我这样吃饭
I am eating normaI.
估计只在你以前住的特兰西瓦尼亚 还是什么国家才算正常吧
Yeah, maybe in TransyIvania, or whatever country you're from.
那我顺便说一声 我来自俄罗斯
Incidentally, I'm from Russia.
而且特兰西瓦尼亚不是个国家 早并入罗马尼亚了
TransyIvania isn't even a country. It's a part of Romania.
你真是个变态
You are such a freak.
嘿 嘿 丹尼
Hey. Hey, Danny.
不准再说这事了 明白吗?
I don't want any more taIk Iike that.
她非得那个样子吗?
But why does she have to act Iike that?
我朋友全都因为她而取笑我
AII my friends make fun of me because of her.
那也许你该换朋友了
Maybe you need different friends.
又也许你该把她送回孤儿院了
Maybe you shouId send her back to the retard camp.
丹尼尔 丹尼尔
DanieI. DanieI.
向你姐姐道歉
ApoIogize to your sister.
她不是我"他妈的"姐姐
She's not my fucking sister.
我明白了
JOHN: I got it.
明白了
Okay.
让我来管
That's me.
道完歉才还你钥匙
You get the key back when you say you're sorry.
今晚想吃点什么特别的吗?
Is there anything speciaI you want me to make tonight?
有没有什么特别爱吃的?
You have any favorites?
喂
HeIIo.
哈哈 你们好吗? 嗨 我们很开心 过的很好
WeII, how are you? Hi, we're great. We're doing good.
她怎么样? 她就在这的 等等
How is she? KATE: She's here, hold on.
嘿 是阿比盖尔修女 要打个招呼吗?
Hey, Sister AbigaiI. Do you wanna say heIIo?
快点 艾斯特 随便打个招呼 我说了 不打
Come on. Esther, just quickIy say hi. I said, no.
呃 宝贝 能帮我挑5个苹果吗?
You know what, do you mind, darIing, can you get five appIes for me?
对不起 她突然有点害羞
Sorry, she got shy all of a sudden.
没事的 我打来是想告诉你...
It's all right. I'm just calling to remind you...
我需要她的病理记录...
...that I'm gonna need her medicaI...
和护牙记录来完成我的监护报告
...and dentaI charts for my supervision report.
她在说啥?
她不怕看牙医
She's not thriIIed about the dentist.
在说你呢
你们相处得如何? 熟悉彼此了吗?
How is everyone doing? Is she opening up to you?
算是吧 几周前她还冲我吐脏话呢
I guess you can say that. She dropped the F bomb on me a few weeks ago.
什么是脏话?
[SIGNING]
可能她开始彻底放开了吧
I guess she's finally coming out of her sheII.
也许吧
Yeah.
她还有犯其他错误吗?
Any other gIitches I shouId know of?
最近出了个大事
We had a big one recently.
是关于她同学布伦达的
It's a girI named Brenda at schooI.
她们在说布伦达
她们在玩操场的滑梯 结果那姑娘摔下来了
They were at the pIayground, there was a sIide, weII, she feII off.
有人说是艾斯特推的
Esther may have pushed her down.
但我没亲眼看到 那姑娘受伤了
I'm not getting the story straight, but she got hurt.
严重吗?
Is she all right?
很幸运 伤了脚踝 其他地方还缝了六针
LuckiIy. She broke her ankIe and had something Iike six stitches.
那可不算幸运
That doesn't sound too Iucky.
很幸运她没摔断脖子
WeII, she's Iucky she didn't break her neck.
你以前说你不会弹钢琴的
You toId me you didn't know how to pIay.
没 我没说过 有 你说过
No, I didn't. Yes, you did.
是你想教我 我跟着学而已
You offered to teach me and I accepted.
好吧 那你就一直假装不会弹吗?
Okay. So then you were just pretending this whoIe time?
我觉得你很想找个人教
I thought you wouId enjoy teaching me.
对你这样热爱音乐的人来说 一个不懂音乐的儿子...
It must be frustrating for someone who Ioves music as much as you...
和一个丧失听力的女儿 肯定让你沮丧至极
...to have a son who isn't interested and a daughter who can't even hear.
等下 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
我进屋的时候 她正熟练的弹着柴可夫斯基的曲子
I waIk in on her pIaying Tchaikovsky without a mistake.
那意味着她一直在骗我
I mean, she's been Iying to me this whoIe time.
她只是想多和你相处吧 不算欺骗
JOHN: She just wants to spend time with you. It's hardIy a Iie.
你不了解
KATE: You wouIdn't know.
她在你面前一直都很乖
You wouIdn't. She's on her best behavior with you.
而在我面前却好似另外一个人
She's compIeteIy different with me.
那你有什么看法?
So, what are you saying?
不知道 她在教室里大声尖叫
I don't know. She threw a fit at schooI.
在操场上推布伦达
She pushed Brenda at the pIayground.
你是想说都是她的错? 不知道 亲爱的 不知道了
Now you're saying that was her fauIt? I don't know. Honey, I don't know.
我不在场 当时是你看着她的
I wasn't there. You were watching them.
噢 算了吧 那只是个意外
Oh, come on. It was an accident.
好吧 那我们不去责备她了
Okay, Iet's not bIame her for anything, fine.
我也去相信她说的每件事
I'II take her word for everything.
也包括你和乔伊斯的事吗?
ShouId I just beIieve what she said about you and Joyce too?
她怎么说的?
What did she say?
她说你和她搞暧昧 什么?
She says that you were hitting on her. What?
噢 她肯定误会了 那只是...
Oh, come on. She must've misunderstood. It was, Iike....
她有叫你去她家吗?
Did she invite you over?
她让我去她家帮忙搬椅子
She asked me to heIp her move a chair.
她说过? 是的 但我婉拒了
She did? Yeah. I bIew her off.
噢 天啊
Oh, God.
为什么不告诉我?
Why didn't you teII me?
因为... 我们本可一笑置之
I We couId've Iaughed about it.
不 我担心... 而你却瞒着我
No, I knew how You were hiding it.
我担心你会像现在这样
Honey, I knew how you'd react.
凯特 凯特
Kate. Kate.
你不能对我交谈的每个女生 都那么敏感
You can't get jeaIous of every woman that I taIk to, right?
八百年前的事儿了 你这话什么意思?
It's been Iike 1 0 years. What does that mean?
说得好像是我的错
You say that Iike it actually means something.
我是最近两年才知道那事的
It's onIy been two years since you toId me.
你知道我有多抱歉 而我现在觉得压根不信任我
You know how sorry I am. I just feeI Iike I've earned a IittIe trust here.
我也给过你机会 不公平 太不公平了
I gave you a second chance. That's not fair. That's not fair.
说清楚点 是不是只能说我的错 而不准提你的?
Let me get this straight. We can taIk about my mistakes, not yours?
我那是病! 你这个想操别人的混蛋!
I was sick! You were an asshoIe who wanted to fuck somebody eIse!
你让我们的孩子命悬一线
You put our chiId's Iife in danger.
我几个月前就可以离开你 而且不会有人怪我
I couId've waIked away months ago. Nobody wouId've bIamed me.
噢 过分了 你过分了 是你妈妈教你这样说的?
Oh, that's sharp. That's sharp. Where did you get that from, your mother?
丹尼 别玩那垃圾了 我得做事
Danny. Turn that crap down, pIease, I gotta work.
好吧 谢谢
Fine. Thank you.
我去吧
ESTHER: I'II get it.
你好 艾斯特 你来这干嘛?
HeIIo, Esther. What are you doing here?
我能进去吗?
May I come in?
我可能搞错了一件事
I'm afraid I may have made a mistake.
艾斯特好像有点问题
There couId be something wrong with Esther.
什么?
What?
什么意思? 你说过她从来不惹麻烦
What? You toId us that you'd never had any troubIe with her.
是的 但麻烦总找上她
I didn't. But troubIe does have a way of finding her.
什么样的麻烦?
What kind of troubIe?
有一次两个女孩打架 她在场
Two girIs get into a fight, there she is.
有人偷东西被抓 她又在场
Someone gets caught steaIing, there she is again.
那又怎样? 难道...? 先让她说完
So? Does that mean ? Just Iet her finish.
你告诉我滑梯事件后 我打去她以前的学校
After you toId me about the girI in the pIayground, I called her oId schooI.
得知有次一个男孩...
WhiIe she was there, there was a boy...
手握剪刀摔了一跤...
...who feII with scissors in his hand...
不小心把手给扎了个大口子
...and accidentally stabbed himseIf through the jaw.
艾斯特同样在场
And Esther was there again.
我不明白了 你都说了是不小心
I don't understand. He accidentally stabbed himseIf.
但最大的麻烦还是沙利文家房屋被烧
But the most troubIing thing is the SuIIivan house fire.
我深入了解了一下 那是纵火案
I checked into it further. It was arson.
犯人一直没找到
They have never found the person who did it.
你到底想说什么呢?
JOHN: What are you suggesting here?
这些事她都有份参与?
That she had anything to do with any of this?
太荒谬了
It's ridicuIous.
我也不愿相信这些事...
ABIGAIL: That a chiId couId commit such crimes...
会出自一个孩子之手
...it fIies in the face of everything I beIieve.
是啊 不会的
WeII, yeah.
家里来了个刻薄的女人 她想带我走
There's a mean Iady here. She's come to take me away.
你能帮帮我吗?
WiII you heIp me?
她有些行为是不好 但...
We've had some behavioraI probIems, but....
但还不至于到那种地步 对吧?
Yeah, nothing Iike that. I mean, right?
有 有的 真的吗 再想想
Yes, we have. JOHN: Really, hon, think about it.
我有试过联系她在俄罗斯的孤儿院
ABIGAIL: I've tried to reach the Russian orphanage where she was raised.
我觉得有必要搞清楚她的背景
I think we need to know what we're deaIing with.
好吧 我来告诉你
WeII, I'II teII you what we're deaIing with.
等一下 别说话 听着
KATE: No, you know what? Stop it. Listen.
她就只是一个九岁大的 父母双亡的小女孩
We're deaIing with a 9 year oId girI who's an orphan, okay?
我们得带她去见见布朗宁医生 那就带她去见见布朗宁医生
We're taking her to Dr. Browning. We can take her to Dr. Browning.
去找树屋的钥匙
[SIGNING]
要玩玩吗? (俄罗斯轮盘赌)
[SPEAKING] Do you want to pIay?
一有新发现我就马上通知你
ABIGAIL: I'II call you as soon as I find anything eIse out.
好的 您保重 好的 非常感谢
JOHN: Right. Take care. KATE: Okay. Thank you very much.
晚点再玩
Maybe Iater.
不会有事的
It's going to be fine.
我们只是吓吓她好让她别再来了
We'II scare her so bad she'II never come back here.
她来了
Here she comes.
去招手让她停车
Wave your arms and make her stop.
麦克斯 去吧
Max, go.
你没事吧? 麦克斯?
You all right? Max?
麦克斯?
Max?
没事吧?
You okay?
别哭了
Stop crying.
抓住脚 帮我把她弄到路边去
Grab a foot and heIp me get her off the road.
快去
Now.
帮我把她藏起来
HeIp me hide her.
你耍了我
[SIGNING]
那不重要
That doesn't matter.
就因为你帮我藏尸体 他们也会把你关进监狱
They'II send you to jaiI just for heIping me hide her.
她要告发我 我只能杀了她
I had to kiII her because she was going to teII on me.
你不会告发我的 对吧?
You're not going to teII on me. Are you?
别担心
Don't worry.
你是我妹妹
You're my IittIe sister.
我不会让你有事的
I won't Iet anything happen to you.
我爱你
I Iove you.
告诉我你都看见些什么
TeII me what you saw.
你在干嘛? 你看见些什么?
What are you doing? What did you see?
我看见你和麦克斯在树屋里
I saw you and Max in the tree house.
其他呢?
What eIse?
其他还看见什么? 什么其他啊?
What do you mean? What eIse did you see?
什么都没看见了 我发誓
I didn't see anything. I swear.
你有告诉别人吗? 没有
Did you teII anyone? No.
我没告诉任何人
I didn't teII anyone.
求你别...
PIease....
如果你骗我 我会切掉你那还没长毛的小鸡鸡...
If I find out that you're Iying, I'II cut your hairIess IittIe prick off...
让你来不及体会它的真正用处
...before you even figure out what it's for.
听懂了吗? 懂了
Do you understand me? Yes.
你尿床了
You pissed yourseIf.
和你聊得很开心 艾丽丝 希望我们能做朋友
It was nice taIking to you, AIice. I hope we can be friends.
非常愿意
I'd Iike that.
我们马上出来 宝贝 你们可以进来了
We'II be right out, honey. You can come on in.
我的第一直觉是...
My initiaI instinct is that...
艾斯特的过去没什么 根深蒂固的大问题
...there's not a deepIy rooted probIem in Esther's past.
那她现在没问题? 也不是
So there's nothing wrong with her? No.
问题还是有 我们需要去关注一下...
It's not all good news. I think what needs to be examined...
艾斯特和她周围人之间的关系
...is Esther's reIationship with those around her.
特别是和你 凯特
Specifically with you, Kate.
你们之间的关系似乎很紧张
It seems she feeIs there's been some reaI tension between the two of you.
是么 她已经尽力讨好你...
Okay. She's doing her best to pIease you...
你却不领情
...but you're bIocking her attempts to bond.
不是那样的 根本不是那么回事 该做的我都做了
是吧? 让她说完
Right? Just Iet her finish.
有些事导致她产生这样的感觉
Something's happening to cause Esther to feeI this way.
也许是你对酗酒或对麦克斯感到内疚
Perhaps it's your guiIt about drinking or what happened to Max.
也许是你自认不是个合格的母亲的情绪...
Maybe some of your feeIings of inadequacy as a mother...
在与艾斯特相处时不自觉的流露
...are manifesting themseIves in your reIationship with Esther.
我不认为我不合适啊
I don't feeI inadequate.
她跟你说了什么啊?
What did she tell you?
她没察觉 她没发现
She didn't see. She doesn't know.
她很白痴
She's so stupid.
艾斯特是个很害羞 缄默...
Esther's a very shy, reserved...
和敏感的小女孩 她正处于最困难的时期
...sensitive IittIe girI going through an extremeIy difficuIt time.
她特别的聪明 善于表达
She's exceptionally bright and highIy articuIate.
只需要多点耐心 多点理解
She just needs a IittIe patience and understanding.
多谢你的"支持"
Thanks for your support back there.
这可是你的主意
That was your idea.
凯特 等等
Kate, wait, wait, wait.
虽然我不是心理医师 但我觉得她说得有些道理
I'm not a psychiatrist, but a Iot of what she said made sense.
要接么?
Do you wanna get that?
你好? 你好 是科尔曼夫人么?
Hello? WOMAN: Hello, is this Mrs. Coleman?
我是 您是?
Yes. Who's this?
我是圣玛丽亚孤儿院的修女朱迪丝
This is Sister Judith from St. Mariana's.
抱歉打扰你 我就是想问下...
I'm sorry to bother you, but I need to know...
...阿比盖尔修女有没有去你那
...if Sister AbigaiI made it to her appointment with you.
来过了 怎么了?
Yes. Why?
她从昨天就一直没回来...
She hasn't returned since yesterday...
我有点担心她了
...and I'm just starting to get really worried.
好了 我问完了
MAN: Okay, I think we're done.
警官 有线索或是疑犯了么?
KATE: Detective, do you have any Ieads or suspects?
还没有 为什么...
MAN: No, not yet. I just don't understand...
发生这事 谁能干出这事? 太....
...this kind of thing. Who wouId do this? It's....
恐怖了
AwfuI.
如果你们有其它线索 电话我们
You think of anything eIse, you give us a call.
嗯 一定
KATE: Yes. AbsoIuteIy.
走了
Let's go.
这些正是阿比盖尔修女说的 看
This is what Sister AbigaiI was taIking about. Look.
"性格障碍儿童" 看这些症状
''Character disturbed chiIdren.'' Look at the symptoms.
"看起来可爱 难交朋友以及维系友谊"
''Superficially charming. DifficuIty at making and keeping friends.''
我觉得修女未必是这个意思
I'm not sure this is what she meant.
她可以拣布朗宁医生想听的说
She couId've toId Dr. Browning whatever she wanted to hear. Look.
"他们善于操纵...
They ''are adroit manipuIators...
常常挑拨他人敌对达到自己目的"
...oftentimes pIaying peopIe off one another to get what they want.''
你打算让布朗宁医生也看看?
Well, you gonna show this to Dr. Browning?
我不打算给她看这些
I'm not showing her anything.
我以后都不见她了
I'm not seeing her anymore.
你什么时候决定的? 你觉得呢?
When did you decide that? When do you think?
你不信任布朗宁医生了?
You're gonna discount Dr. Browning?
为什么你不怀疑其他人有问题 单单只怀疑我呢?
Why does everyone get the benefit of the doubt from you except for me?
如果需要帮手照顾孩子们 我们可以找一位
If you need heIp with the kids, we can arrange that.
我不需要
I don't need heIp.
只是想了解她多一点
I just wanna know more about her.
她从哪来 她是谁
I wanna know where she came from, and I wanna know who she is.
假如阿比盖尔修女是对的?
What if Sister AbigaiI was right?
如果有人身处危险 我们自己的孩子...
I mean, if someone was in danger, our own chiIdren...
难道你不想搞清楚? 我当然想
...wouIdn't you wanna know? Of course I wouId.
我会和她以前的俄罗斯孤儿院联系
I'll contact the orphanage she came from in Russia. All right?
这是初步打算
I mean, it's a start.
怎么了? 嘿
What? JOHN: Hey.
好吧
Fine.
我想知道你是否有收到来自 Sludyanka孤儿院的消息
I was wondering if you'd heard from anyone at the SIudyanka SheIter.
阿比盖尔修女曾提过 她要...
Sister AbigaiI had mentioned that she wouId
你查了
Oh, you did.
我不明白 为什么没有她在那的记录呢?
I don't understand. How can they have no record of her being there?
好的 谢谢
Yes, pIease.
如果你一有消息请马上电话我 谢谢
CouId you just call me as soon as you know anything, pIease? Thank you.
艾斯特 该走了
JOHN: Esther, we gotta go.
艾斯特?
Esther?
被你吓到了
You got me.
怎么了? 我不想去看牙医
What? I don't want to go to the dentist.
为什么呢? 就是不想去
Why not? I just don't want to go.
害怕了? 不是
What, are you scared? No.
那就下次吧
We're gonna rescheduIe, though.
如果你乖乖的和我一起画画 你今天就可以翘课了
Tell you what, I'll Iet you pIay hooky if you want to come and draw with me.
好吧
All right.
等会 丹尼尔
KATE: Wait, DanieI.
你们和艾斯特处得如何?
How are you two getting aIong with Esther?
还不错
Fine, I guess.
是么? 嗯 妈妈
KATE: Yeah? DANIEL: Yeah, Mom.
她有没有让你们感到不安...
But has she ever made you feeI, I don't know, uncomfortabIe...
...或者有没有做什么不该做的事?
...or has she done anything that she's not supposed to do?
没有 比如 有没有伤害过你们?
No. Like, has she ever hurt any of you?
没有
DANIEL: No.
确定?
You sure?
好吧
Okay. All right.
只有我们俩真好
ESTHER: I Iike it when it's just the two of us.
你都想不到我等了多久才等到 像你这样的父亲
You don't know how Iong I've waited for a daddy just Iike you.
还有母亲 对不?
Mommy too, right?
我觉得妈妈不太喜欢我
I don't think Mommy Iikes me very much.
错了 妈妈爱你的 没什么的
That is not true. Mommy Ioves you. It's all right.
爱领养孩子当然不可能像 爱自己孩子一样多
It must be hard to Iove an adopted chiId as much as your own.
宝贝 你同丹尼和麦克斯一样 都是这个家的一部分 明白么?
Sweetheart, you're just as much a part of this famiIy as Danny and Max. Okay?
为妈妈做点什么 让她知道你爱她
Do something nice for Mommy. Show her how much you Iove her.
真是个好主意
That's a wonderfuI idea.
我有个惊喜要送给你 妈妈
I have a speciaI surprise for you, Mommy.
真的?
You do?
我为你摘了这些花
I picked these fIowers just for you.
艾斯特 你做了什么呀? 天哪 我的胳膊!
Esther, what did you do? God. ESTHER: My arm!
你为什么要这样做? 爸爸 我的胳膊!
KATE: Why did you do this? Daddy, my arm!
约翰! 嘿
KATE: John! Hey.
为什么要这样做? 嘿 停手 停手
KATE: What did you do? JOHN: Hey. Stop, stop.
为什么要这样做?
Why did you do this?
天呐 她故意的 不是
Oh, God. God, she did this on purpose. No, no, no.
就是的 亲爱的 不是
Yes, she did. Hey. Honey, no.
她明明清楚这些玫瑰对我意味着什么
She knew what these roses meant to me.
我的错 亲爱的 不该让她讨好你
It's my fauIt, hon. I toId her to do something nice for you.
真不敢相信
I can't beIieve this.
爸爸!
ESTHER: Daddy!
Daddy!
爸爸 爸爸!
Daddy, Daddy!
怎么了 宝贝?
What is it, honey?
我的手好痛啊
My arm still hurts.
看看好吗? 你会没事的
Can I have a Iook at it? You're okay.
我会轻轻的 没事的 宝贝
I'll be gentIe. It's all right, honey.
天呀
Oh, my God.
得马上送你去医院
We need to take you to the hospitaI.
你是个非常勇敢的女孩 知道么?
JOHN: You're a brave IittIe girI, you know that?
医生说你很快就能痊愈了
Doctor said you're gonna heaI reaI fast, okay?
你拉断了她的胳膊
You broke her arm.
不可能 我根本没用力拉她
KATE: It's impossibIe. I didn't grab her that hard.
她今晚想睡这 也许你该谁楼下去
She wants to sIeep in here tonight. Maybe you shouId sIeep downstairs.
今晚来客人了
I'm having guests for dinner.
不用找了 谢谢
You know, you can have it. Thanks.
过得开心
KATE: Have a good day.
丹尼尔
DanieI.
你的书
Your books.
怎么回事? 让我看看你的书包 我也不知道
What happened? Let me see your bag. I don't know.
才买的啊 把书捡起来 要不都湿了
We just bought this. Pick it up, it's gonna get wet.
妈妈!
Mom!
麦克斯! 不! 救命!
KATE: Max! No! HeIp!
麦克斯!
Max!
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我在这 妈妈在这 没事了 宝贝
I'm here. Mommy's here. You're okay, honey. Come on.
抱着你了 宝贝 没事了 对不起
I got you. Yeah. Oh, baby, it's okay. I'm so sorry.
我明明挂在停车档 还拉了手闸
I remember I put it in park and I set the brake.
麦克斯没说艾斯特做了什么
Max didn't indicate that Esther did anything.
麦克斯在 包庇她 而且不止这一次
Well, Max is covering for her. And I don't think it's the first time.
这也不是第一次你把自己犯的错 推到艾斯特头上
It aIso wouIdn't be the first time you bIamed Esther for your own mistake.
我不希望她继续待在这里
You know what? I want her out of this house.
你打算让人把她领走了?
You're ready for somebody to come and take her?
是的 我不在乎
I am. I don't care.
我会不惜一切代价保护我的孩子
I will do whatever it takes to protect my chiIdren.
女孩们早上发现了这个
The girIs found this this morning.
女孩们发现 你是说艾斯特发现的吧
The girIs found it. You mean Esther found it.
是艾斯特 有区别么? 她说谎了?
Yes, Esther. Does it make any difference? Is she Iying?
你需要帮助
BROWNING: You need heIp.
我们在康复中心为你做了预定...
We've reserved a pIace for you in a rehabiIitation faciIity...
离这仅45分钟路程
...about 45 minutes from here.
我没喝
KATE: I didn't drink it.
买了两瓶 往水池子里倒了一瓶
I bought two bottIes. I poured one of them down the sink.
不是这个? 不是
But not this one? No.
约翰 我快一年滴酒未沾了
John, I haven't had a drink in aImost a year.
我们是想帮你 如果你还在欺骗自己...
We wanna heIp you, but there's nothing we can do...
我们就没办法了 我没说谎 我是想喝
...untiI you stop Iying to yourseIf. KATE: I'm not Iying. I wanted to drink it.
你都不知道我他妈的多想喝 但我没喝
You have no fucking idea how badIy I wanted to drink it, but I didn't.
我没喝 假如麦克斯受伤了....
I didn't drink it. If Max had gotten hurt....
今天早上的事跟这个没有一点关系
What happened this morning has nothing to do with this.
没法信你
I find that hard to beIieve.
我滴酒不沾的唯一原因就是为了麦克斯和丹尼尔
The onIy reason that I'm sober is because of Max and DanieI.
一想到你若因我酗酒而离开 且酿成大祸...
I think about what wouId have happened had you not been there...
我会杀了我自己的
...and it makes me wanna kill myseIf.
我不会做任何事...
I wouId never do anything...
让这种情况发生 不会
...to Iet something Iike that ever happen again. I wouIdn't.
太煽情了
That is so manipuIative.
我知道没有理由让你相信我
I know I haven't given you reason to beIieve me, I know I haven't.
我对你说谎了 我该告诉你的
I Iied to you. I shouId have toId you about this.
我会接受治疗 我会去该死的戒酒互助会 如果这是你希望的...
I'll go to therapy, I'll go to fucking A.A. if that's what you want...
但你一定要相信我 我不信
...but you have to beIieve me. I don't.
你必须相信我 约翰 这事你必须信我
You have to beIieve me. John, you have to trust me on this.
你有一周的时间考虑是去康复中心...
I'll give you a week to go to rehab...
还是我带孩子们走
...or I'm Ieaving and I'm taking the kids with me.
这样很公平 是吧?
I think that's fair, okay?
我会尽力帮你 让你尽快恢复
I'll heIp you as much as I can, make it really easy.
妈妈下午会过来
Mom's gonna come in the afternoon.
好吗? 我很愿意 愿意帮你度过难关
All right? I'm willing to do this. I'm willing to try and figure this out.
都看你了 如果你敢讲出去我就枪毙了你妈妈
But it's up to you. I'll shoot Mommy if you tell.
麦克斯 麦克斯 你没事吧?
Max. Max, are you okay?
她做了什么? 是她动了手脚导致车祸的?
What did she do? Did she do something to make the car crash?
你看见了 就要帮我 这样爸妈才可以保护我们
If you saw her, you have to heIp me, so Mom and Dad can protect us.
他们无能为力的
[SIGNING]
为什么?
Why not?
这是阿比盖尔修女?
Is that Sister AbigaiI?
麦克斯 她在我树屋里干嘛?
Max. What did she do in my tree house?
她把不好的东西放进去了
那些不好的东西还在么?
Are the bad things still there?
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.
我会把那些东西从树屋取出来 这样他们就会信我们了
I'll get the stuff from the tree house. Then they'll have to beIieve us.
要去哪啊 凯特? 你在这做什么?
Going somewhere, Kate? What are you doing here?
她很好 别吵醒她
She's fine. Let's not wake her.
回你自己房间去
Go to your room.
不用再假扮了 对么?
HonestIy, we're past that now. Aren't we?
我知道你想干什么
I know what you're doing.
我不会让你伤害我孩子一丝一毫的
I will not Iet you hurt my chiIdren.
我?
Me?
我又不是那个喝得醉醺醺的 害麦克斯在池塘溺水的人
I'm not the one who passed out drunk and Iet Max aImost drown in the pond.
要不是约翰...
If it wasn't for John...
她就死了 而你也该在牢里待着了
...she'd be dead, and you'd probabIy still be in jaiI.
谁告诉你的?
Who toId you that?
非常隐私
It's very intimate.
让我了解了很多 还给我
I Iearned so much. Give it to me.
杰西卡 还有背叛你的丈夫 艾斯特 还给我
Jessica. Your cheating husband. Esther, give it to me.
酒瓶藏在哪了
Where you hide your wine bottIes.
我... 我警告你
I'm I'm warning you right now.
"医生宣布噩耗时 她还在踢我...
''She was still kicking when the doctor toId me...
而那只是幻觉...
...it was something called phantom...
胎动的幻觉
...fetaI movement.
16天来 我怀着已经夭折的孩子'' 住嘴 艾斯特
For 1 6 days, I carried my dead baby.'' Stop it. Esther.
''是我能想象到的最残忍的折磨''
''It was the crueIest torture I couId imagine.''
闭嘴 你给我闭嘴
Stop it. You stop it.
你到底怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
凯特 太晚了 都是你的错
Kate, it's too Iate. It's your own fauIt.
你把这个家庭当成 理所当然的
You took your famiIy for granted.
你什么意思? 你想干吗?
What do you mean? What are you going to do?
打我?
Hit me?
我们是从你们那领养的 你居然说你们完全不了解她?
We adopted her from you. How couId you not know anything?
沙利文有可能是非法收养她
The Sullivans couId have adopted her illegally.
她记不起任何对我们有帮助的事情了?
She doesn't remember anything that could help us?
我会再打的
I'm gonna call you back.
''Saarne机构''
''Saarne Institute.''
谢谢
你好 你会说英语吗?
Hello. Do you speak EngIish?
你会说英语吗?
Do you speak EngIish?
不好意思 有没有人会说英语?
Is there anyone who speaks EngIish there?
事情紧急
This is very important.
不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're saying.
喂? 是Saarne机构吗?
Hello? Is this the Saarne Institute?
是的
Yes.
我想询问你们机构一个孩子的情况
Yes. I need to taIk to somebody about one of your chiIdren.
她被一户美国家庭所收养 是女孩
She was adopted by an American famiIy. It's a girI.
她不可能是这儿的
She is not come from here.
我还没说她的名字呢
Well, I haven't even toId you her name yet.
你不明白 Saarne机构不是孤儿院
You do not understand. Saarne Institute is not an orphanage.
而是精神病院
It is a mentaI hospitaI.
你是在找这个吗?
Are you Iooking for this?
可怜的阿比盖尔修女
Poor Sister AbigaiI.
这种事儿我一个人可做不来 麦克斯和我一样有罪
I couIdn't have done it myseIf, you know. Max is just as guiIty as I am.
不管麦克斯做了什么 都是你逼她的 想想看
Whatever Max did, you made her do it. Think about it.
她怎么可能知道东西藏在这里?
How did she even know what was up here?
证据还是烧了好
It's aIways better to burn the evidence.
如果被找到 他们不仅会追究我
If they find these things, they won't just be coming for me.
也会追究麦克斯
They'll be coming for Max too.
你真想这样? 等等
Is that really what you want? Wait.
你做什么啊?
What are you doing?
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
放我出去!
Let me out!
Let me out of here!
妈妈!
Mom!
是Saarne机构 S A A R N E Saarne
It's called the Saarne Institute. S A A R N E, Saarne.
在爱沙尼亚
It's in Estonia.
爱沙尼亚? 不可能 她的资料都来自于俄国
Estonia? No, this can't be right. All of her paperwork is from Russia.
我正给他们传照片
I'm sending them a picture of her right now.
或许她的生母是那儿的病人
Maybe her birth mother was a patient there.
或许她还出生在那儿
I don't know. Maybe she was even born there.
妈妈!
Mom!
救命!
HeIp!
妈妈! 爸爸!
Mom! Dad!
天哪!
Oh, God!
天哪 打911!
Oh, God. Call 91 1 !
别担心 你要上天堂了
Don't worry. You're going to heaven.
天哪!
KATE: Oh, God!
天哪! 丹尼尔!
Oh, my God! DanieI!
快走开! 别靠近大火!
Move away! Move away from the fire!
丹尼尔?
DanieI?
上帝啊 丹尼尔? 妈妈来了 你能听见吗?
Oh, God, no. DanieI? Mommy's right here. Can you hear me?
快醒醒 亲爱的 妈妈就在这儿
PIease wake up. Honey, Mommy's right here, okay?
你会没事的
You're gonna be all right.
腹部出血已止住 但他颈部受伤严重
We stopped the abdominaI bIeeding, but he has a very serious neck injury.
目前情况稳定 你们很幸运
He's stabiIized for now. You shouId consider yourseIves very Iucky.
我们能见见他吗? 再过会儿
Can we see him? DOCTOR: In a IittIe whiIe.
他正在重症监护室
He's resting in the ICU.
他能告诉我们事情经过吗?
Okay. And will he be abIe to tell us what happened?
有可能
DOCTOR: It's possibIe.
要等他醒来才能知道他是否 记得发生的事情
No way of knowing for sure what he'll remember untiI he wakes up.
失陪
Excuse me.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
我知道你心力交瘁 我也是
JOHN: I know you're exhausted and upset, and so am I.
肯定有其他什么解释 她不会来自精神病院
There has to be some other expIanation. She didn't come from an insane asyIum.
你所认为的孤儿院对她一无所知
The orphanage you thought she came from has never heard of her.
她的一切可能就是个谎言
Everything about her couId be a Iie.
一切 我们有她的护照 出生证明 学校档案
We have her passport. We have schooI records, medicaI records.
医疗档案 她来自于半个地球以外的国家
These are papers from around the worId.
这是什么? 就是一张纸
What is this? It's a piece of paper.
这次你妈也在场 不是我胡乱猜测
Your own mother was there this time. It wasn't just me. Your mother was there.
纵火的要么是艾斯特要么是丹尼尔
It's either Esther or DanieI who started the fire.
你认为是谁? 我不知道
Who do you think it was? I don't know.
我受够了 不会再帮你串接这些疑点
I'm so done. I'm done connecting these dots for you.
你爱怎么想我怎么想
You know, you can think whatever you want about me.
如果你想 我今晚就可以离开
I will Ieave tonight. If that's what you want, I will Ieave tonight.
但有一个条件 艾斯特也必须离开
On one condition. Esther goes too.
能给我1美元去买汽水吗?
Can I have a dollar for the soda machine?
你妈让你待在这儿
Your mother wants you to stay right there.
给你 别去太久
There you go. Don't be too Iong.
我去找艾斯特
[SIGNING]
好
Okay.
怎么了 亲爱的?
What? What is it, sweetie?
重症监护室 心脏停跳
MAN [O VER SPEAKER]: Code 99, ICU.
Code 99, ICU.
让开 让开 妈 看着麦克斯
MAN: Coming through, coming through. Mom, take Max.
快去304房! 急救车! 让让!
WOMAN: Let's go, Room 304! Crash cart coming through! Move, peopIe!
丹尼尔? 疏散走廊人群!
KATE: DanieI? MAN: CIear the hall! CIear the hall!
你在外面等着 他心脏停跳 别进来
You have to stay out here. He's in cardiac arrest. Stay out here.
丹尼尔!
DanieI!
开始 输液
WOMAN: Here we go. MAN: Start a drip.
检查血压 检查换气功能
WOMAN: Check BP, pIease. MAN: Check ventiIation.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
有脉搏了
MAN: We got a puIse. We got a puIse.
凯特
Kate.
你做了什么? 你对他做了什么 贱货?
What did you do? What did you do to him, you bitch?
住手!
JOHN: Stop, stop!
保安! 保安! 她要杀死我的孩子!
WOMAN: OrderIies! KATE: She's trying to kill my baby!
爸爸! 拉住她!
Daddy! HoId her!
她想杀死我的孩子!
KATE: She's trying to kill my baby!
拉住她
HoId her still.
放开我
KATE: Get off me.
拉住她 拉住她
HoId her still. HoId her still.
好了 别激动
Okay. Easy, easy.
你还好吗? 没事了
You okay? There you go.
(1个未接来电)
凯特 丹尼尔
Kate. DanieI.
他们还在检查 明天才能知道结果
They're running tests. We shouId know more tomorrow.
别担心丹尼尔 他会没事的
Don't worry about DanieI. He'll be okay.
过几天就能回家了
He'll be home in a few days.
你要留在这里好好休息
You need to stay here, get some rest.
我带麦克斯和艾斯特回家
I'm gonna take Max and Esther home.
约翰
Johnny.
请别让她靠近麦克斯
PIease don't Iet her near Max.
我爱你
I Iove you.
[SIGNING]
丹尼会没事的
好梦
[SIGNING]
闭上眼睛
嗨 爸爸
ESTHER: Hello, Daddy.
你怎么穿成这样子? 你喜欢吗?
What are you wearing? Do you Iike it?
上帝啊
Oh, Jesus.
瞧瞧你 脸怎么抹成这样? 这是干嘛?
Look at you. What have you done to your face? What is this?
我不想一个人待着 我害怕
I don't want to be aIone. I'm scared.
我爱你 爸爸
I Iove you, Daddy.
我也是 亲爱的
You too, hon.
我真的好爱你
I really Iove you.
我知道
I know.
约翰 让我照顾你
John, Iet me take care of you.
你在干嘛? 干嘛呢?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
你哪根筋不对了? 这是做什么?
What's gotten into you, huh? What's going on?
你说你爱我
You said you Ioved me.
你完全搞错了
You are so confused.
我对你不是那种爱
You know what? I don't Iove you Iike that.
那是凯特和我相爱的方式
That's the way Kate and I Iove each other.
明白吗?
You understand?
没看出来
I don't see that.
你得尊重你妈 我尊重的
You have to respect your mother. I do.
我只是觉得只有我一人尊重你
I just feeI Iike I'm aIone sometimes in respecting you.
从没有其他人能体会你的感受
I don't think anyone ever thinks about what you might be feeIing.
我真的很在乎你 约翰
I really care about you, John.
我知道 艾斯特
Yeah, I know, Esther.
我只是...累了
I'm just I'm tired.
非常累
I'm very tired.
我不知道该怎么做 太难了
And I don't know what to do. It's difficuIt.
一切都崩塌了
I mean, everything is just falling apart...
上帝啊 我好担心丹尼尔
...and, oh, my God, I'm so worried for DanieI.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
你是个好人 约翰
You're a good person, John.
是个好爸爸
You're a great father.
还是个帅气的男人
And a handsome man.
上帝啊!
Jesus Christ!
天哪 快别这样!
My God, stop, stop, stop!
什么都别说 上楼去! 回你的房间!
Just stop taIking and go upstairs! Go to your room!
别把我当做小孩 我明天就给朱迪丝修女打电话
Stop taIking to me Iike I'm a chiId. I'm calling Sister Judith tomorrow.
讨论一下你的将来 我受不了
We're gonna have a conversation about your future in this house.
再也受不了了
I just I can't do it anymore.
随你
ESTHER: Fine.
艾斯特
Esther.
喂? 你是凯瑟琳 科尔曼吗?
Hello? MAN: Is this Katherine Coleman?
喂? 我是
Hello? Yeah. This is she.
我是Saarne机构的瓦拉瓦医生
My name is Dr. Varava. I'm calling from the Saarne Institute.
我刚看了你传给我的照片 你认出她了吗?
I've just seen the picture you e maiIed. And do you recognize her?
她现在在哪儿? 能听见你说话吗?
Where is she right now? Is she somepIace where she can hear you?
她不在我身边 正和我丈夫在家
No, she's not with me. She's with my husband at home.
马上打电话给你丈夫 让他转移家人
Call your husband right now, and tell him to get your famiIy out of the house.
然后报警 他不肯听我的 为什么报警?
And then call the police. He won't Iisten to me. But why?
那就告诉他照片里的不是真正的小女孩
Then tell him the little girl in the picture is not really a little girl.
而是个成年女子 什么?
She's a grown woman. What?
你说什么? 我传给你的照片
What are you talking about? The picture I sent you...
是我们收养的女儿 她才9岁
...is of our adopted daughter, and she's 9 years old.
不是的
No, she's not.
她患有罕见的荷尔蒙失调症 又叫垂体机能减退
She has a rare hormone disorder. It's called hypopituitarism.
导致身材矮小 只是看上去像个孩子
It causes proportionaI dwarfism. She onIy Iooks Iike a chiId.
根据记录 丽娜 克莱姆生于1976年
According to our records, Leena KIammer was born in 1 976.
今年33岁
She's 33 years oId.
不可能 肯定弄错了
This can't be. This is a mistake.
为了你们的安全 我也希望如此 她有疤痕吗?
I hope so, for your sake. Does she have the scars?
什么? 我不知道 什么疤痕?
What? I don't know. What scars?
丽娜是我们院最具暴力的病人之一
Leena was one of our most vioIent patients.
她在这儿时 我们给她穿拘束衣 (把胳膊紧紧拴在身体上的长袖外衣)
When she was here, she was kept in a straitjacket...
防止她伤害到工作人员
...to stop her from hurting our staff.
但她总是不停挣扎想逃脱
She was constantly fighting to get out.
衣服勒入她的皮肤 在腕部和颈部留下疤痕
It cut into her skin and left her with scars around her wrists and neck.
你们不可能看不到啊
There is no way you could not have seen them.
她为什么会在你们医院?
Why was she at your hospitaI?
她非常危险暴力 就我们所知已杀害七人
She's dangerously ill, violent. She killed seven people that we know of.
上帝啊 她怎么会骗得倒我们?
Oh, my God. How couId she fooI us?
她很多时候都是装成小女孩到处行骗
She has been passing herself off as a little girl for most of her life.
爱沙尼亚的一户人家因为受骗收养她
She tricked a family here in Estonia into adopting her.
她勾引养父未遂 就杀了他和他一家子
When she couIdn't seduce the father, she killed him and his whoIe famiIy.
然后还纵火烧了房子 是的 你怎么知道?
Then she burned the house down. Yes. How did you know?
她一年前消失 杳无音讯
She disappeared a year ago and we Iost track of her.
如果她真是丽娜 你得赶紧行动了
If it's really Leena, you don't have much time.
艾斯特?
Esther?
拜托 约翰 快接电话啊
Come on, Johnny. Come on. Pick up the fucking phone.
他妈的
Shit.
快接啊
Come on.
天哪!
Oh, God!
拜托
Come on.
快接
911 什么事?
WOMAN [O VER PHONE]: 91 1. What is your emergency?
我要报警 家中有人入侵
I need the poIice. We have an intruder in our home.
快接啊
Come on.
(凯特来电)
(2个未接来电)
我是约翰 约翰?
JOHN [ON RECORDING]:This is John. John?
约翰 这是我的电话 目前无法接听
You've reached my cell, but I can't pick up.
他妈的!
Oh, fuck it.
约翰?
John?
约翰? 约翰?
John? John?
不要啊 上帝!
No, God!
麦克斯
Max.
搞什么!
What the fuck?
就在那儿 别动
[SIGNING]
别动 就躲在那儿
艾斯特! 不许伤害她!
Esther! Don't you hurt her!
别伤害她! 我在这儿!
Leave her aIone! I'm here!
艾斯特!
Esther!
我知道
I know.
回去 太危险了 回去
Go back. It's too dangerous. Go back.
求你了
PIease.
别让我死 妈妈
Don't Iet me die, Mommy.
我才不是你妈妈!
I'm not your fucking Mommy!
宝贝 没事了
Baby, it's okay.
孤儿怨
-=结束=- 谢谢观看